<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Chris Engstrom</title>
    <link>/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Chris Engstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Scenery</title>
      <link>/blog/change-of-scenery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/change-of-scenery/</guid>
      <description>It’s weird to look back a week ago and think about how much has changed since then. For those of you who don’t know, I recently made the decision to leave T&amp;amp;S and join the ColorfulStudio crew.
Recently I have been considering whether or not T&amp;amp;S is the right company for me. I love the people that work there and the environment of the company, don’t get me wrong, but when you are thinking about your career and where you want it to go in the future you have to take a step back every once in a while and look at what your goals are for yourself and if you will be able to achieve them at your current job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Birds of Northwest Expressway</title>
      <link>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</guid>
      <description>So right when we moved in we noticed a couple of barn swallows started to build a nest of mud. Instead of being jerks we figured we would let them build their nest.
We grew kind of attached to them and it was kinda cool to see them swoop in as you are walking out and such. Well soon enough we noticed they had laid eggs and were kind of excited about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>So here I am, on a Saturday afternoon, wanting to work on my site. The problem…is that I don’t know quite how to do that yet. I recently got a job at T&amp;amp;S Web Design but I am still a noob at creating a web site. It was hard to catch on to the whole process to begin with but I think I am getting the hang of how they have it set up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>