<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>old site on Chris Engstrom</title>
    <link>/tags/old-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in old site on Chris Engstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/old-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Scenery</title>
      <link>/blog/change-of-scenery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/change-of-scenery/</guid>
      <description>It’s weird to look back a week ago and think about how much has changed since then. For those of you who don’t know, I recently made the decision to leave T&amp;amp;S and join the ColorfulStudio crew.
Recently I have been considering whether or not T&amp;amp;S is the right company for me. I love the people that work there and the environment of the company, don’t get me wrong, but when you are thinking about your career and where you want it to go in the future you have to take a step back every once in a while and look at what your goals are for yourself and if you will be able to achieve them at your current job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Isnt This Working?!?!</title>
      <link>/blog/why-isnt-this-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-isnt-this-working/</guid>
      <description>When working with JavaScript or jQuery it is important to remember to check and make sure that the basic functionality is working correctly before you get frustrated and upset that absolutely NOTHING is working.
Recently I was working on a project at work and no matter what I did with my jQuery statements, I couldn’t get anything to work. I was looking at examples online and making sure mine was following the same concept but still nothing was working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML/CSS Horizontal Menu</title>
      <link>/blog/html-css-horizontal-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/html-css-horizontal-menu/</guid>
      <description>/* HTML/CSS Horizontal Menu Post */.horizontal-menu {list-style: none;margin: 20px 20px 70px !important;padding: 0;width: 525px}.horizontal-menu li {display: inline;position: relative;}.horizontal-menu li a {text-decoration: none;padding: 5px 0;width: 100px;background: #32522b;color: #eee;float: left;color: #8292A0;font-weight: bold;text-align: center;border-left: 1px solid #121212;}.horizontal-menu li a:hover {background: #92C088;color: #252B30}.first_menu_item {border: none !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiddling With Javascript</title>
      <link>/blog/fiddling-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/fiddling-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Intro While I was at work the other day we received an update request from a client. Since I saw it first I assigned it to myself and started to work at it. There were only two things that the client wanted us to change. The first was changing the suite number for a particular address, which took about five seconds to track down and change. The second was that he wanted to post a job on their careers page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Birds of Northwest Expressway</title>
      <link>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</guid>
      <description>So right when we moved in we noticed a couple of barn swallows started to build a nest of mud. Instead of being jerks we figured we would let them build their nest.
We grew kind of attached to them and it was kinda cool to see them swoop in as you are walking out and such. Well soon enough we noticed they had laid eggs and were kind of excited about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DROID Incredible by HTC</title>
      <link>/blog/droid-incredible-by-htc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/droid-incredible-by-htc/</guid>
      <description>The news of Alltel in my area being bought out by Verizon had me quite excited when I had first heard about it. At that time the Google Nexus One was just about to be released and I didn’t know there was going to be a correlation. Soon after I had heard Alltel was getting bought out I also found out that the Google Nexus One would be coming to Verizon in the Spring of 2010!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>/blog/mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>I know I am late because Mother’s Day was this past Sunday. I didn’t actually forget, thank you very little, I just found a neat plugin that I wanted to try out called Smart Youtube that lets you embed youtube videos into your WordPress site really easily. I posted this video on my mom’s Facebook wall to remind her of what it is like when I am home. Here goes nothing…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>So here I am, on a Saturday afternoon, wanting to work on my site. The problem…is that I don’t know quite how to do that yet. I recently got a job at T&amp;amp;S Web Design but I am still a noob at creating a web site. It was hard to catch on to the whole process to begin with but I think I am getting the hang of how they have it set up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>