<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Chris Engstrom</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Chris Engstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:32:37 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Birds of Northwest Expressway</title>
      <link>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-birds-of-northwest-expressway/</guid>
      <description>So right when we moved in we noticed a couple of barn swallows started to build a nest of mud. Instead of being jerks we figured we would let them build their nest.
We grew kind of attached to them and it was kinda cool to see them swoop in as you are walking out and such. Well soon enough we noticed they had laid eggs and were kind of excited about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DROID Incredible by HTC</title>
      <link>/blog/droid-incredible-by-htc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/droid-incredible-by-htc/</guid>
      <description>The news of Alltel in my area being bought out by Verizon had me quite excited when I had first heard about it. At that time the Google Nexus One was just about to be released and I didn’t know there was going to be a correlation. Soon after I had heard Alltel was getting bought out I also found out that the Google Nexus One would be coming to Verizon in the Spring of 2010!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>/blog/mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>I know I am late because Mother’s Day was this past Sunday. I didn’t actually forget, thank you very little, I just found a neat plugin that I wanted to try out called Smart Youtube that lets you embed youtube videos into your WordPress site really easily. I posted this video on my mom’s Facebook wall to remind her of what it is like when I am home. Here goes nothing…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>So here I am, on a Saturday afternoon, wanting to work on my site. The problem…is that I don’t know quite how to do that yet. I recently got a job at T&amp;amp;S Web Design but I am still a noob at creating a web site. It was hard to catch on to the whole process to begin with but I think I am getting the hang of how they have it set up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>