<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web development on Chris Engstrom</title>
    <link>/tags/web-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web development on Chris Engstrom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Scenery</title>
      <link>/blog/change-of-scenery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/change-of-scenery/</guid>
      <description>It’s weird to look back a week ago and think about how much has changed since then. For those of you who don’t know, I recently made the decision to leave T&amp;amp;S and join the ColorfulStudio crew.
Recently I have been considering whether or not T&amp;amp;S is the right company for me. I love the people that work there and the environment of the company, don’t get me wrong, but when you are thinking about your career and where you want it to go in the future you have to take a step back every once in a while and look at what your goals are for yourself and if you will be able to achieve them at your current job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Isnt This Working?!?!</title>
      <link>/blog/why-isnt-this-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-isnt-this-working/</guid>
      <description>When working with JavaScript or jQuery it is important to remember to check and make sure that the basic functionality is working correctly before you get frustrated and upset that absolutely NOTHING is working.
Recently I was working on a project at work and no matter what I did with my jQuery statements, I couldn’t get anything to work. I was looking at examples online and making sure mine was following the same concept but still nothing was working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML/CSS Horizontal Menu</title>
      <link>/blog/html-css-horizontal-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/html-css-horizontal-menu/</guid>
      <description>Many pages that I have seen that are organized pretty well have horizontal menus, so I want to teach myself how to do them and get good at it. My alterior motive to writing this post is that I need one of these to use for a jQuery post I originally planned on doing before this but forgot the css code back at work. So here I am about to do it again but this time understand it better than I did the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiddling With Javascript</title>
      <link>/blog/fiddling-with-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/fiddling-with-javascript/</guid>
      <description>While I was at work the other day we received an update request from a client. Since I saw it first I assigned it to myself and started to work at it. There were only two things that the client wanted us to change. The first was changing the suite number for a particular address, which took about five seconds to track down and change. The second was that he wanted to post a job on their careers page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>